module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'The movie "Amadeus" is about which famous composer?', 
      a: 'Beethoven', 
      b: 'Mozart',
      c: 'Bach',
      d: 'Handel',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Opera originated in which country?', 
      a: 'France', 
      b: 'Germany',
      c: 'England',
      d: 'Italy',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: "You'll hear this piece each 4th of July with fireworks and canon shots:", 
      a: "Beethoven's 9th Symph", 
      b: 'Flight of the Bumblebee',
      c: '1812 Overture',
      d: 'Canon in D Major',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is arguably THE greatest operatic tenor of the modern era?', 
      a: 'Luciano Pavarotti', 
      b: 'Placido Domingo',
      c: 'Andrea Bocelli',
      d: 'Josh Groban',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Philip Glass composes in what musical style?', 
      a: 'Romantic', 
      b: 'Minimalism',
      c: 'Baroque',
      d: 'Jazz',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which type of trumpet has NO valves (buttons to press)?', 
      a: 'B-flat', 
      b: 'Piccolo',
      c: 'Tooter',
      d: 'Bugle',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: "An orchestra's Concert Master holds what position?", 
      a: 'Conductor', 
      b: '1st Violin',
      c: '1st Flute',
      d: '1st Horn',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many keys on the modern piano?', 
      a: '104', 
      b: '88',
      c: '56',
      d: '206',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which one is NOT a percussion instrument?', 
      a: 'Snare', 
      b: 'Marimba',
      c: 'Double Bass',
      d: 'Triangle',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'One of the most important jazz saxophonists of all time:', 
      a: 'Miles Davis', 
      b: 'Billie Holiday',
      c: 'John Coltrane',
      d: 'Maynard Ferguson',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};